We are Angerme!
Our new single will be released on June 14.
We would like to introduce our new single "Ai no Kedamono" and the music video for "Dousumujin"!
We would like to take a look at "Ai no Kedamono" here!
Here you go!
I am fun
I'm so excited to be here!
Oh!
Wow.
That's so cute.
You're gonna make Winn look so cute.
Wow.
Oh!
That's so cool!
I can see the sparkles.
That's awesome!
It's so cool!
The sunflower is smeared.
So cool!
Sunflowers.
Wow!
What's this? That's great!
That's awesome!
It's so cool!
What?
Open it.
I think it's cute.
It's cute.
That's it.
It's sexy.
It's cute.
This one is black.
I love it! I like it! I like it!
Because someone is really cute.
It's Rao.
Wow!
How do bugs feel?
From a bug's point of view.
It's true.
That's amazing.
The insect's point of view.
It's good.
Wow!
It's cool.
It's really cool.
Is this bad?
No, it's not.
Woo!
It's so cool!
This is bad.
This is so cool.
Everyone is so cool.
They're cute.
Cute.
Seriously,
YO!
It's so good.
I see it, I see it.
Aya, all this.
They're fangs.
Yes.
Yay!
LOL!
Laughing.
Yay!
I'm zinc-free,
Oh, here it comes!
Wow!
Wink-o!
That was a big wink-o.
Leila's not here yet.
Leila-san's not here yet.
Not yet.
Did you go yet?
Did she go yet?
I was kind of hoping for that.
It's a square deal. It's like right now.
He said it to me.
It's like a face.
A
Akira is cute!
She's cute!
Wow.
She's cute.
A
Mafia.
Mafia?
Mafia
a political party
And next
Wow.Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
Cool.
Oooooooooo
Ooooooooo
Ooooooooooooooooooo!
Yay!
That's great!
It's so good!
Lady Leila!
Miss Leila!
You're so beautiful!
So beautiful!
You're right!
It was another day of terror.
No one could tell.
So good!
You look great!
All I wanted to do was to love
What a conversation!
I love
People's habits
퍼 biggest hit
So good!
Very nice.
The best hit is guauo.
We're all in it together.
Oh, my God.
flies
ni
I can only see one more
I can only see one more.
Yes, it is.
Limited, limited, limited.
If you're interested, take a look.
Like this.
This is awesome.
It's too cool.
It's so cool.
What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
Here he comes.
It was so good.
He was so cool.
It's easy to be the front.
There were only people who said they weren't talking.
I'm not talking.
Please come in. Miss Leila.
Please come in, Leila-sama.
But I'm making a lot of mistakes.
But there was a statue of Leila-sama, wasn't there?
The teacher said so much about it during the music video,
Leila-sama!
When I saw the music video, he said "Leila-sama".
It was super Leila-sama.
Everyone says "Leila-sama" together, right?
When you do it together, you do it like this.
Everyone do it like this.
Like this.
And then, I see it here.
And then, they would say "Leila-sama".
Yes.
Please look at it a lot.
Thank you very much.